https://economycashcarry.com/privacy-policy/

Economy’s Best
60th Anniversary (2018)
Economy’s Best
60th Anniversary (2018)
Economy Cash & Carry Privacy Policy
At Economy Cash & Carry (economycashandcarry.com), we respect the privacy of our online users. Our goal is to provide you with a personalized internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant to you. In order to achieve this goal, we sometimes collect information during your visits to understand what differentiates you from each of our millions of other users.The following statement demonstrates our commitment to your privacy and outlines the privacy practices for the Economy Cash & Carry website and includes what personally identifiable information of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.What information is collectedEconomy Cash & Carry collects certain information from and about its users in two ways: directly from the user and from our web server logs.User-Supplied Information:When you submit a form, such as our contact form or sign up for our newsletter, we may ask you for your name, email address, and other personal information. The more accurate your information, the better we can customize your online experience with Economy Cash & Carry.Web Server Log Information:When you visit an internet website, you disclose certain information about yourself, such as your internet protocol (IP) address, the time of your visit, and the referring location (e.g., the site or page that offered a link to an Economy Cash & Carry webpage). Our website, like many other websites, records this basic information about visits to the website. You should remember that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, your information can be collected and used by others. Although Economy Cash & Carry tries to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. You are also solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords you set up and/or any account information.Economy Cash & Carry works with third-party data analytics. Some of these companies may use anonymous information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide data and targeting recommendations based on which we may provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.This website uses Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the site. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of this website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.How and when information is usedWe use information in different ways, depending on the type of information:User-Supplied Information:This information is used for purposes such as personalization and visitor verification.Web Server Log Information:This information helps us identify which areas of our site are of interest to our visitors. Economycashandcarry.com also collects the (IP) addresses of its visitors for the purposes of system administration.How we protect your informationThe privacy and protection of your personal information is vitally important to us. At this time, Economy Cash & Carry does not make personal information available to any third parties without your permission. This may or may not change in the future without notification. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective partners regarding your economycashandcarry.com usage are provided in aggregate form and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user.Your access to some services and content is password protected. If you created an account with economycashandcarry.com, we recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Economy Cash & Carry will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. You should not disclose your username and password to others.In addition, if applicable, you should remember to sign out of your economycashandcarry.com account or service at the end of each session. You may also wish to close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or internet cafe.Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, despite our efforts to protect your personal information by using the latest security technology, Economy Cash & Carry cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, or to or from our online products or services. You transmit all such information at your own risk. However, once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.Who has access to the informationEconomy Cash & Carry may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to protect the rights or property of economycashandcarry.com.We welcome any questions or comments you have about economycashandcarry.com.
CONTACT
Main Corporate Office1000 E. Overland Ave.El Paso, TX 79901(915) 532-2660 Cash & Carry El Paso, TX 799011500 E. Paisano(915) 533-8240 Distribution WarehouseEl Paso, TX 79901100 S. Cotton(915) 838-7473 Hours of Operation:Mon through Fri 8:00 AM – 5:00 PMSaturday 8:00 AM – 2:00 PMSunday Closed
PRIVACY POLICY
Menu
PRIVACY POLICY
Search
Sign up for email updates. Get the latest updates on savings, special offers, new items, events and more.
© 2020 Economy Wholesale Grocers • All Rights Reserved  • Site Designed and Managed by PixelMark
